(Raj:)Okay, first order
of Physics Bowl business.
(Raj:)We need a truly kick-ass team name.
Suggestions?
(Howard:)How about the Perpetual Motion Squad?
(Howard:)It's beyond the laws of physics,
plus a little heads up for the ladies.
- The ladies?
- Perpetual Motion Squad...
(Howard:)...we can go all night.
- I like it.
- I don't.
(Sheldon:)Teams are traditionally named after
fierce creatures...
...thus intimidating one's opponent.
We could be the Bengal Tigers.
(Sheldon:)Poor choice. Gram for gram...
(Sheldon:)...no animal exceeds the relative
fighting strength of the army ant.
(Raj:)Maybe so, but you can't incinerate
a Bengal tiger with a magnifying glass.
(Leonard:)Let's put it to a vote.
- All those in favor...
- Point of order.
(Sheldon:)I move that any vote on team names
be unanimous.
(Sheldon:)No man should be forced to emblazon
his chest with a Bengal tiger...
(Sheldon:)...when common sense dictates
it should be an army ant.